Mystery Date is a comedy, romance film directed by Jonathan Wacks.
Tom McHugh quickly learns that his perfect big brother Craig isn't all he's cracked up to be while on a night on the town with the girl next door, during which Tom is harassed by unpleasant strangers, threatened by mobsters, pursued by
police, attacked by an irate florist, accused of murder, and has his date kidnapped—all because everyone thinks he's Craig...and the classic 1959 DeSoto Firesweep he borrowed off his brother has two dead bodies in the trunk.
Tom McHugh, played by Ethan Hawke.
Geena Matthews, played by Teri Polo.
Craig McHugh, played by Brian McNamara.
Dwight, played by Fisher Stevens.
Sharpie, played by Tony Rosato.
Doheny, played by Don S. Davis.
Mystery Date is a 1991 American dark comedy film directed by Jonathan
Wacks, and starring Ethan Hawke, Teri Polo, and Brian McNamara.
Shock-rockers Gwar have a brief cameo in the film.
The film explores themes of date, mistaken identity, neighbor, girl next door.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.